(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.2",
"generated_at": "2026-08-21T01:03:27.686596",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
同じ未来を見たい
I want to see the same future,
あの夢手に入れたい
I want to make that dream mine,
それぞれ違ったココロで走れgo
with each of our different hearts, run, go!
どこを見ても真っ暗な場所に芽生えてた
No matter where I looked, in the pitch-black darkness, it sprouted,
ほんの小さな希望にこの瞳奪われた
this tiny speck of hope captured my gaze.
不安で揺れる心を上手くチューニングして
Tuning my wavering, anxious heart just right,
ほんの小さな勇気を振り絞っていたよ
I mustered up a tiny bit of courage.
諦めの文字デリートして進む
Deleting the word "give up" and moving forward.
苦しいときも もう私はひとりじゃないから
Even when things are tough, I'm not alone anymore,
だからもっと夢追いかけたい ワクワク止まらない
so I want to chase my dreams even more, my excitement won't stop!
想像越えてく 世界見せてあげる
I'll show you a world that surpasses imagination.
アクセスしてみたい 後悔なんてさせない
I want to access it, I won't let you have any regrets.
それぞれ違ったココロで彩れ
Color it with each of our different hearts!
架空の空に輝く眩しい想いは
The dazzling feelings shining in the fictional sky
見たことのない光を現実に届けるよ
deliver a never-before-seen light to reality.
いつも聴こえるエールをここにキャプチャーして
Capturing the cheers I always hear right here,
また新しい光を探したくなるよ
makes me want to search for a brand new light.
君の笑顔は保存して進む
Saving your smile as I move forward,
悲しいときに 見返すよ力が湧くから
gives me strength to look back whenever I feel sad.
胸を張って夢追いかけたい 奇跡の物語一緒に作ろう
Chest high, I want to chase dreams, let's create a miracle story together!
終わらない夢を 誰一人欠かせない
An endless dream, with not a single person missing,
愛が舞ったこの世界 それぞれ違ったココロで彩れ
in this world of dancing love, color it with each of our different hearts!
悲しいときも 寂しいときも 信じ合えるものがある
Even when sad, even when lonely, there's something we share in belief.
忘れずにこの鼓動鳴らし続けたい
I want to keep making this heartbeat echo without forgetting.
終わらない世界に 溢れ出るよ笑顔達
Smiles overflow into an endless world.
憧れの舞台立ちたい らしく輝きたい 踏み出そう奇跡の一歩を
I want to stand on my dream stage, shine like myself, and take a miraculous step!
憧れの舞台たちと 楽しく輝きたい
I want to shine happily on the stage of my dreams
時には涙出して
Sometimes shedding tears,
また笑い合いたい
I want to laugh together again
同じ未来を見たい
I want to see the same future
あの夢手に入れたい
I want to grasp that dream
踏み出そう 奇跡の一歩を
Let's take that miraculous first step
息切らせ夢追いかけたい
Breathless, I want to chase my dreams,
ワクワク止まらない
My excitement never stops
想像越えてく 世界見せてあげる
I'll show you a world beyond imagination
アクセスしてみたい
I want to try accessing it,
後悔なんてここにない
There's no room for regrets here
それぞれ誓った 心で進むわ
Moving forward with hearts each sworn to
We're here! We're here!
Hi everybody!
Welcome everybody to the HoloMyth 3D collab showcase!
Domo, Same desu! It's me, Gawr Gura!
Shinigami desu desu.
Ino neko!
Ame, Koomori shinshi wa down.
I'm Takanashi Kiara from Hololive English!
This is our special showcase, we just performed the classic Shiny Smily Story!
This is the official HoloLive English stage.
Everybody has done it. The first one was Risu.
Our Takamori week!
Gura me weekend!
Yeah! Yay!
I feel like Gura's showcase was very different from the usual stuff, right?
I was a pain in the butt of the studio, but studio team,
arigatou gozaimasu!
Too much math, I hope everybody enjoyed it.
Yes, I was a pain. It's okay, though!
And then Ame, Ame, you were so fun! Yeah!
I was really glad, I'm glad I was able to do it. So many balls!
But now I'm excited for this stream! Yeah! So excited!
We have so many things for winter stream—
Wait, wait, wait, wait! This is a special occasion, isn't it? We're in 3D together properly for the first time!
Right? Look at these bodies, these beautiful bodies! We've sang and danced.
If you guys want, you're welcome to use the hashtag up there! Hashtag #Myth3DKitaaa! This way, this way!
Hashtag #Myth3DKitaaa! Yes! Take screenshots, screenshots of it! Do it, do it, do it! Post them on Twitter or Facebook, I don't know.
It's not often that we get together like this, so we're gonna make the most out of this occasion with—we have two games that will be playing!
And also, if you want, like that Chanyany's story, right? You want more? Yes, yes, yes! But I'm sorry if you wait until the very end of the stream, you might see more of those performances, it's worth it!
Yay! Yay! Yay! Yay! Yes! Okay, well, cool.
Then, I think we should start with the first game, shall we? Sure! Cool!
Give me, give me, give me, give me... game? What, we're going somewhere? No, huh? Yes, it's a good game! A good game!
According to the stream? No, no, no, no! Let's play it this way. No, come this way! Okay, let's go. Yeah, why not? Okay. Yes, not the game, okay? Okay.
Why are we here? Welcome! What do you mean welcome?
We're not supposed to be here! You guys are under arrest!
What? The Investigation 3D Redux? Wait, if there's a logo that means that was actually planned!
I didn't know about this! I didn't know about this! Did you guys know? No! All right.
Well, I need to investigate all of you closely, because now we're in 3D and now we can.
Did you do something? This looks so good! I bet you think someone is guilty! You did! You did! You did! You did!
What did you do? What did you do? What did you do? What did you do?
There's a crime or something here? Hold on, I gotta look closely. Let me see. Take a picture!
Oh! Oh! You want to look closely? Yeah, yeah, I heard you got an update or something.
Let me, let me get something changed recently. I'm gonna have to protect myself, so let me just get something to protect protect myself!
You guys remember seeing Kiara's behind? Oh god! She has a weapon!
No, no, no, no, no! That's fake! That's that's not real!
It's popsicle.
It's a popsicle.
All right, turn around. Turn around. Let's get a look.
Okay!
Oh man. I'm not hiding any crimes in here, only good things.
That's a crime!
You got a permit for that? Don't be— Yeah, do you have a permit for this, ma'am?
Kiara is the one that's going to get this channel banned!
All right. All right, I need to archive this, so we'll take a picture of the front first, okay?
All right.
A photo for all the crimes you've committed.
All right, side profile.
Is that too wet? Nice.
Okay, enough, enough.
The back? Yes, the back!
All right, all right, all right, all right. Now the close-up look.
Oh my god!
Okay, all right, all right, all right, all right. Get out of here.
You got a good angle.
Kiara, thanks for the photo shoot.
Now, who's next? The small one.
You.
Oh, that's you.
Go shorty! Go shorty!
That's too short.
Get in there.
She definitely has crimes, though.
You got any crimes?
Me?
Yeah, being too short. That's what it is. What are you talking about, shorty?
Short stack, you want to go?
I'll tell her. You want to go?
Alright, alright, alright, alright, alright, alright.
Put 'em up! Put 'em up! Put 'em up!
Oh, pretty good.
All right, let me have a closer look at that thing.
It's a violation.
What violation?
That thing back there. What's this thing?
It's a kind of smelly.
Not smelly.
Smelly.
Hold out. Catch it. Catch it.
Is that smelly?
All right, let's take a picture of this. Let's take a picture of the front first, okay?
Front.
Oh, my mugshot, okay.
Yeah, mugshot time.
All right, side profile, turn please.
She looks guilty.
Guilty! Guilty of crimes!
Guilty of being too cute. Glasses?
Possibly. All right, now stay right here.
Calliope Mori, come into the frame, please.
Why am I involved?
I did nothing.
Is she your lost child?
I need to compare heights, sizes.
Oh, sorry about that.
It's all right. You kind of morphed into you for a minute there.
Look at that height difference!
It's pros.
It's froze!
It froze!
All right, all right, shark, get out of here.
All right, see you later, guys.
Out of the frame, I got to take a picture.
No, no, no, no, no.
Calliope Mori committed crimes.
What did I do?
Every Calliope crime.
Well, I guess I did kill everyone on the planet.
So you admit to it.
Okay, but that's my job, okay?
All right, let me inspect her ankles.
Suspicious.
Oh!
Look at your shoes.
These are nice.
What are you? What are you doing with these shoes?
What size are the baby boots?
The dog's barking. The doggy's barking.
Step on me! Step on me!
No. Call, please.
I didn't do any.
All right, you did something. You're being booked.
And uh we're gonna take your picture first, so face the front, please.
I'm the most innocent one here.
I think she has a weapon.
A weapon?
No weapon.
I think she should pat down.
I didn't bring it today.
Guilty! Killproof all the way!
She looks so guilty.
Look at that!
All right, the side profile.
All right, all right, get out of here. You're going downtown.
It's an act. It's all an act.
Okay, last! The most offensive...
crimes against humanity!
Guilty now.
Your turn.
She couldn't be.
She's definitely the most guilty.
What?
I'm innocent!
Really?
Yeah, that's why you're booked.
Because too many puns.
Your crimes...
Wait, wait, you guys enjoy it!
I know you guys enjoy it.
Yeah, yeah.
Also, she's not giving out enough cookies. She promises cookies and she doesn't give them.
I do give cookies!
It's rough times.
Okay, I can't. She gave us cake the other day.
Are you hiding?
Tentacles in back there?
Let me pat you down.
Are you hiding tentacles back here?
No, no, no.
Is there something there?
Let me see.
Go ahead for a second.
Oh, fuck.
Hazukashii.
What is that?
What is that?!
Tentacles!
He's got tentacles!
She's got tentacles!
I feel yucky.
Be innocent! Nothing wrong.
Look at that way.
Okay, okay.
That's dangerous.
So slimy.
Almost lost my breath.
Because she's so cute.
Get out!
Get the hell out.
All right, get though.
She put them away.
Oh, no, they're not going away.
They're going away!
Don't touch me! Don't touch me!
They're creepy! They're creepy!
Okay, okay.
You'll be fine.
Catch! Stop!
Maybe close your eyes.
Oh, then it's fine.
Now she looks normal.
Me to the men.
Are they gone?
They're gone. Okay.
Okay, please are they gone?
Okay, okay, they're gone."
Collect that disgusting...
Disgusting.
Oh, sorry.
All right, we're going to take your picture. Come on. Okay, I'll free you after this. I swear, I swear, I'm sorry.
I didn't mean that. That's cruel.
I'll do it!
All right, side profile, please.
How could she commit any?
Cute!
All right, I need to test something for science.
Give me a moment.
Let me put my mushimegane away.
Okay!
What do I do?
Oh boy!
What is that?
Um, I need to do a scientific dunk.
No, Ina, stay.
I need you to stay still.
It's not going to work!
Do the dunk!
Yay!
All right, one more time.
All right, one more, one more. Do the dunk, please. Swim dunk.
She's short!
Yay!
Very nice.
Okay, okay. All right, that concludes the investigation. I'll free you for now.
No, it doesn't.
But no, we have one more. Let's get it.
No, we have one more. Let's get it.
Yeah, we have the other one, the criminal.
I don't think so.
You're not getting away.
You're not getting away from us.
You're not getting away from us! Get her!
Be careful, be careful! That was a terrible crime.
Come here, come here!
Get her! Get her! Get her away! Stick him away!
Get her! Get her away! Take her away!
I'm going to be here.
But there was something.
You can't do it like this.
That's not professional!
You got to investigate professionally.
Okay, fine, fine.
Once you guys get those.
Amizone. Amizone.
Let me look at you. You guys got to do my stats.
Now, let's see.
Set the Watson concoction over there.
I've committed no crimes! Those are just possessions!
You committed one.
30 seconds ago.
She's a liar.
Not hold on. What do we arrest you on?
Now hold on. What do we arrest you on?
What are you guys looking at?
Oh, cute.
Oh, nice shoes.
They're pretty good.
Yeah, they're so shiny. Investigative steppers.
Don't hide.
There's nothing there.
What are you hiding under the cape?
She's hiding the Watson concoction!
There's nothing there! They can't see it!
Shh, I can't see it.
But they wish they could.
Well, we should take some photos too. Yeah, let's shot some photos too.
Get against the wall, yellow one.
Get against the wall.
Oh, she's guilty! Look at her face!
I cannot—no, no.
Look at that face. What are we looking for, chat?
All right. And her side?
What are we looking for?
I would never commit a crime! Investigating us without warrants, illegal substances!
Well, we'll have to use this—this footage investigated later in the back.
Well, we'll have to use this footage investigated later in the back.
But for now, we have to actually go by the script, okay? Enough of this.
Go by the script! We have some games prepared, so let's do the girls.
Get rid of this all. Put this back in the... mushimegane.
Yeah, put those back where you found them, okay? I need those.
So, everybody, are you ready for some fun?
Yes! Yes! Maybe.
I'm up for anything. The first game that we're playing today is...
Telephone Charades!
Telephone Charades
[Title: Telephone Charades]
Well, since we're here in the highest quality of 3D,
we want to show it off to you guys with this special game.
I will explain the rules to you guys.
Okay.
Rules, rules, rules.
I love rules.
Rules are my favorite! Right?
The first person—we're going to stand in a line, okay?
In a line.
And the first person on the either most right-hand or the most left-hand side...
And the first person on either the most right-hand or the most left-hand side...
...will get a clue that everybody else doesn't get to see.
We have to close our eyes. Yes.
And then the person taps on the next person's shoulder, and they may open their eyes and they act—well, for example, if Calli's first, Calli's first...
And then the person taps on the next person's shoulder, and they may open their eyes and act—well, for example, if Calli's first...
...she will act out to the other person, which she is. Yes.
And then we only have 30 seconds for that, and there's no talking allowed!
So, how will that go, I wonder? You got to do your best...
...to show everything with your body. All right?
Okay, so we'll go by order of Calli, please, on the right.
Yeah, over there, you would perfectly fit in—in the spot.
Yeah, over there, you'll be perfectly in the spot.
Okay. And then Ame, please.
Ame, come on.
Okay.
Then Ina.
That's me.
Gura! Gura, gura, gura, gura.
And it will be me! Let's see how that goes. Okay.
All right. Well, everybody, close your eyes.
All right. Everyone, close your eyes.
Okay, let's start.
Not looking. Don't look, don't look, don't look.
Answer: Octopus
This is going to be interesting.
No talking, 30 seconds!
Can I turn around? Can I turn?
I think so. All right, Ame.
Check this out.
I'm not looking.
What the heck is this supposed to be?
Oh, okay. I think I'm ready. I think you're ready.
Okay. Can I look?
Yeah, Ina, look.
Okay, do your best. Gambate, gambate.
Okay, do your best. Ganbatte, ganbatte.
Very nice.
Yeah, keep it up. Oh, I think I get it.
You like it? Are you ready to go on?
I don't know! Just copy—just copy what...
Put your back into it! Ina, put your back into it!
What's happening?
I don't know. What's happening?
You got to really move with it.
You gotta really move with it.
Okay. Okay. You got it. You got it.
Nice legs.
Hi!
Okay, pretty good.
Ooh, okay.
Wow. Wow. Wow.
I feel things I have never felt before.
Can I stop now?
Yeah, you can stop now!
I would say that is um... mating dance?
I would say that is, um... a mating dance?
Are you serious?
Yes.
What part of that looked anything like a mating dance?
Mating dance!
Does a mating dance look... was mine... was I...
What did you think it was, Gura?
Yeah, what did you think it was?
I um... started like... interpretive dance.
I, um... started like, uh, interpretive dance.
Ohh.
Okay.
Wait, what did you think?
Well, I I thought it was swimming.
That's what I thought.
Swim? That's more like drowning.
What the fuck did you think this?
I was like...
That's what Kelly did!
Okay. Okay.
Octopus!
You should have seen the way I was moving my limbs! It was insane!
I... I didn't know. I would have known, of course.
Maybe, right? It's too difficult. No, it's not.
I did my best, though. There are only four limbs, right?
Well, okay. That was okay, I guess.
We'll do a second round, all right?
We'll switch up the order, so who wants to go first?
I'll... I'll fix what you couldn't do, Calli.
I do not want to be last.
Oh no! Oh no! Oh no! What the fuck?
Okay, maybe outside a Family Mart.
The next one, however, will be more like a situation rather than an animal or whatever.
And you guys will not see the answer either until the end, so have fun guessing with us, all right?
Everyone?
You better get it right, chat. Close your eyes!
I'm trusting you guys. Trust in each other!
Do your best, Ina.
How am I gonna do?
Oh, wait.
I think I got it. I think I got it.
Okay, okay. You can turn around, Calli.
Okay, what do we got? Stop talking.
(Ina acting)
Got it? That's kind of cute.
Wow, cute.
Open your eyes.
Hi.
(Calli acting / making noises)
I mean, you're making noises, though.
I'll forgive that one. You're not talking.
Pull my finger.
I mean, okay.
Can I turn around? All I have to do is...
She didn't pull my finger!
What are you doing to me? You can't use-
Is that it?
(Kiara making noises)
Okay, that's cute.
That's cute.
Okay, all right. I think I might guess it.
All right.
Oh, that's easy.
That's easy. That's easy.
Okay. It seems easy.
When is a genius?
Memory, sleepy, sleeping, thinking of-
There's a little more to it.
Well, I guess it was sleeping on someone's shoulder, right?
That's what I thought. That's what I thought!
In the grand-
I didn't know it was on your shoulder.
That's why I was so close to you.
Oh yeah, yeah.
Okay. Well.
Okay, so the correct one is falling asleep on someone's shoulder.
We did say chat.
I was so easy!
We didn't say what.
We did say what?
I know. We did say what?
Hey, what could go wrong, right?
We didn't mess up.
Okay, so we got both wrong.
Now which shoulder would you like to sleep tonight?
Which shoulder would you like to sleep on? I got plans.
Isn't it nice to sleep on somebody's shoulder?
Mine?
Anywhere.
Anytime, Calli.
I got two pillows right here, you know?
Coca-Cola. Pretty comfortable. It's pretty much a blanket.
When you sleep, her hair is going to be really soft.
It's like a singer outside. Got to make it.
That thing is soft and squishy. What are we talking about? Squishy.
Outfit's firm. Good try, everybody!
It was fun! Yay!
We didn't get it at the end, but it was pretty close to the second one.
We did. Yeah.
I would say half, we have 0.5 points, I would say.
Not bad. Pretty good.
Hey, did you guys enjoy the chat?
Got to talk in chat, did you enjoy it?
Did you guys get it right?
Yeah.
Well, that was fun.
Is anyone saying no?
Anyone saying no? I will get...
Don't you dare.
You, and you, and you...
No, I'm kidding.
All right. Okay.
Well, with that, I think we're going to play the next game right away,
because we're excited! We're excited! Wait, which way? Which way?
Wait, we're going which way? Game is over?
What? I'm enjoying it.
Wait, the next game...
We're going to go to another room, though.
Why? You guys got to come with us.
New room! New room!
Come on, let's go. Might as well. Come on.
Where are we going?
Tatatarataa!
I know this place. Tatami room.
It's cozy. It's an office room.
Yeah. Oh, wow, it's nice in here.
Mm, yummy! Tatami!
Well, welcome back, everybody! Thank you for waiting.
Yes, this place, you got it right.
Japanese tatami space, thank you for waiting as well!
Hey, wait a minute, is this her persona?
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no!
That's right, that's right, that's right. It's cute.
She's currently out buying milk, she'll be back soon, probably. Hope she comes back.
Yeah, I do.
So, since it is a Japanese-inspired room, the game, of course, it also is Japanese-inspired,
but before we get started with that, I want to hear some episodes from you guys,
because we all are now together in Japan, some of us for the first time, some of us maybe for the second time, some of us like for the hundredth time, but I think we all kind of felt some kind of culture shock, right? Up until now.
That's true, yeah.
Surely we all have something like that. Japan is very different.
So, anybody got something?
Oh, I do! I do!
Uh, sometimes I got to take a taxi, um, for for various reasons. Whenever I do though, um, the taxi dude is always like,
'Okay, so what's our route?' I'm like, 'Huh? What do you mean what's our route?'
'I'm going to leave it up to you.' He's like, 'Well, we'll take this street, and then we'll take this highway. Is that okay?'
I'm like, 'Yeah, that's fine. And then'
'when we get off, we'll take this street, but this street is a little far, so we're going to take this street instead.'
'It's a shortcut. Is that okay?'
I'm like, 'Yeah, just you know, drive, the car is cool. It's cool.'
It's safer for me to fly.
I know.
Yeah.
I appreciate it.
Speaking of taxis, you know how, you know, when you try to open the door from the taxi,
cause normally you do that in my country, right?
They say like, 'No, no, please don't touch it. We're opening it automatically.'
So please stop, don't touch.
Also when you want to get out, same thing, it always opens automatically.
So I'm like, 'Oh, okay.'
I got used to it now, but it's nice when you have a lot of stuff in your hands though,
cause you don't have to touch the door.
Yeah, yeah.
That's true.
That's true, agree.
Any other episodes?
Hi! Hi! Hi! Hi!
The trains here are insane and crazy!
The train! Densha wa sugoi!
All the train, train stations are like dungeons!
They're crazy.
Oh, yeah.
Kind of scary.
You get lost.
Yeah, you get lost.
You get lost, absolutely.
Yeah, but it's fun, it's like an adventure.
I like it. It's amazing.
I'm worried about you. You get lost a lot, indeed.
No! It's fun, it's an adventure.
Whenever we go out, you guys all follow me like a single file!
We have to remember like mother duck, push the mother duck, I...
one time you walked too far ahead and we were like, what?!
You didn't even check. We walked online a lot.
You gotta keep up. There I was like, oh no, I'm so lagging still.
speaking of trains, one thing I noticed with the trains is that in my country everybody's is like loud and they wake and they scream and listen to music
Speaking of trains, one thing I noticed is that in my country everyone's so loud, awake, screaming, and listening to music...
but in Japan, they're all quiet and they look like they're sleeping.
...but in Japan, they're all quiet and look like they're sleeping.
Yes, very quiet. Right? I'm not scared at all.
And how do people not hold on to the things? They just stand there with power stance.
And how do people not hold on to things? They just stand there with power stance.
Well, I can't really. I hope I could I wish I could. I hold on to Ina.
Well, I can't really... I wish I could. I hold on to Ina!
Yeah, surfing practice. I was like hold on to me, girl. I got you.
Oh, well there's lots of there's lots of text everywhere like there's lots of advertisements and signs and it's crazy and it's fun to test to see what I can and cannot read which is good. I wish I could read all of it.
There's lots of text everywhere, advertisements and signs, and it's crazy! It's fun to test what I can and cannot read. I wish I could read all of it...
Sorry, overwhelming, though, right? It is, but it's also fun 'cause it's something I've never experienced.
...because it's so overwhelming, right? It is, but it's also fun 'cause it's something I've never experienced.
I'm sorry, I took her on one of her first days. I took her to the most overwhelming stores ever.
I'm sorry, on one of her first days, I took her to the most overwhelming stores ever!
Bic Camera, and Don Quijote, and...
I was also following you like a baby chicken. Yeah. I felt like a happy chicken mother, I guess. Anyone else?
Oh, well, I have one. I mean, I tried not to, but I ordered a lot of Uber Eats souls here. Every time I like they like ping pong on my door and like open the door for them, they're like little bow.
Oh, well, I have one. I mean, I tried not to, but I ordered a lot of Uber Eats here. Every time they ping-pong on my door and open it for them, they do a little bow!
And I'm just like, oh, they're so polite even like even I'm not like in front of them. And like, you know, they usually have like a little little message they can send when they say like thanks for the tip.
And I'm just like, "Oh, they're so polite," even when I'm not right in front of them. And you know, they usually have a little message they can send saying 'Thanks for the tip!'
They are so polite, they're like, they're going, hey, Japan. Wow, those are some nice stories you got for me. Thank you very much.
They are so polite, they're like... Wow, those are some nice stories you got for me. Thank you very much!
Thank you very much. Pretty cool.
Thank you, pretty cool!
With that, we're going to play the game to hopefully learn even more about Japanese counters. So the game's name is... What is it called? What is it called, Kiara? It's not written there anymore.
With that, we're gonna play the game to hopefully learn even more about Japanese counters! So the game's name is... What is it called? What is it called, Kiara? It's not written there anymore.
日本の作法王決定戦
[Queen of Japanese Etiquette]
So, the rules are we get one theme, one situation, or something like that, and then, uh, with the theme comes four different choices.
So, the rules are: we get one theme, one situation, or something like that, and with the theme comes four different choices.
There's one wrong one and we'll have them be acted out by everyone. Or we can all do it. How about we just all do it? Everyone get it?
And then once we're done acting, we'll decide together, we'll put our heads together and we'll think which one is wrong. All right. Okay. So, YouTube chat! Let's go. Let's go down.
And then once we're done acting, we'll decide together, we'll put our heads together and we'll think which one is wrong. Alright! Okay, YouTube chat, let's go!
Daily Life 日常生活
[Daily Life / 日常生活]
Then let's look at the first one. The first... Who's acting?
Q1.Daily Life -日常生活- 家では靴を脱ぐ
[Q1. Daily Life: Taking shoes off indoors]
Oh, taking shoes off indoors. We're definitely not doing that right now. Oh, this is really bad actually.
Hopefully Fubuki-sempai won't get mad at us for stepping on her tatami mats. I mean, we're wearing her shoes on here, so I'm sure it's fine, right?
Sorry! There's slippers. See? What is it? But normally there's like a genkan. What's genkan in English? Entrance.
Sorry! There's slippers! See? But normally there's like a genkan. What's genkan in English? Entrance.
And there's a little, little, what do you call it? The stair. The one stair. And before that, you always have to take off your shoes.
And there's a little... what do you call it? The step? The one step? And before that, you always have to take off your shoes.
And a lot of like buildings too, they usually have like spare slippers you can wear. You take shoes off even in like public buildings. Recording studio.
And a lot of buildings, too, they usually have spare slippers you can wear. You take shoes off even in public buildings! Recording studios!
I've actually tripped on one of those where it's got like the indents like a place. I was coming for the first time and I tripped on it. God, I hated it.
I've actually tripped on one of those where it's got like the indents, like a step down. I was coming for the first time and I tripped on it! God, I hated it.
Q1.Daily Life -日常生活- 相手の話の合間に“なるほど”をはさむ
[Q2. Daily Life: Interjecting with short phrases like 'Yes', 'I see']
And is... Interjecting when someone's talking with short phrases such as 'Yes', 'I see', etc.
You can do it to me because I want to say after living in Japan, more and more I noticed that I was getting that into my body.
And when I came back home to Austria, my family, my friends, they noticed. They're like, 'Kiara, you keep on reacting to what I'm saying.'
And when I came back home to Austria, my family and friends, they noticed. They're like, 'Kiara, you keep on reacting to what I'm saying!'
So, but actually I can't get rid of it anymore. What about active listening?
So, actually I can't get rid of it anymore! What about active listening?
Especially like when you're talking on the phone and stuff, like they don't know if you're so listening, right?
Especially like when you're talking on the phone and stuff, like they don't know if you're still listening, right?
Is that good to say like hmm hmm hmm? It's like hmm back to them like most people do.
Is that good to say like hmm hmm hmm? Like hmm back to them, like most people do.
So did you girls also start doing that on your own by now? Oh yeah, I do.
Definitely. Oopsies. I do it.
Amelia, what about you? You haven't been here for that long, but like
Sometimes I feel like it's something I would do anyways. I yeah. Really?
Sometimes I feel like it's something I would do anyway. Yeah. Really?
Naruhodo. Naruhodo.
"Naruhodo" (I see). "Naruhodo".
But I've been told that it's pretty cute, so I will ever continuing it in you.
But I've been told that it's pretty cute, so I will continue doing it with you.
Okay, next up!
All right, Kiara, this one's for you. You're the one who's been blowing your nose for the past week.
This is true. Exposed! Exposed!
I'm not sure about this. I don't think this is Is this like separating
the trash, like the garbage and recycling? They separate the trash a lot, yeah.
But then like the tissues?
But then what about the tissues?
What other tissues are playing in this game? Are we doing something wrong?
Like, what other tissues are playing in this game? Are we doing something wrong?
No, we're all oldling, so.
That's separating the tissue.
And then it also in different trash bags? No way.
And then, in different trash bags? No way.
No way. Well, I mean, we could we could put this one aside
No way. Well, I mean, we could put this one aside
and come to think of it, what the last option is.
and think about what the last option is.
No, no. Yeah, let's look at the last one. Next up, last one.
Expressing your gratitude before and after meals.
It's like that. Let's start. Let's start.
Let's start. Let's start. Let's start.
Itadakimasu. They got it.
Itadakimasu and gochisousama deshita. Beautiful.
Itadakimasu means I'm digging in and gochisousama deshita means thank you for the meal.
They do in the inside that. We all know that. See?
They do inside out. We all know that, see?
Easy peasy! You need the answer, Kiara. Do you even have to think?
I don't think we have I've already forgotten them, so never mind.
It's okay. I think I remember. Yeah.
So the wrong one is number three!
Yay! Good job!
Number three.
Compliant. That's wrong. You wouldn't do that, right? That'd be too much work.
It's like, yeah, this one I like wiped my food, you know, on the station, and this one I blew my nose on like. That's too, too much.
It's like, yeah, this one I wiped my food, you know, on the station, and this one I blew my nose on, like... That's too much.
It all gets burned! Yeah! Trash is trash.
It's box. Oh, that was that one pretty well. Oh.
It's box. Oh, that one went pretty well. Oh.
Okay, what's next? What shall we do next?
Okay, so we're done. I think we really did so perfectly we don't even need a second round.
Okay, but okay, there's something important that everybody needs to pay attention to.
What?
I'm listening.
We want to show off our merchandise one more time!
Everybody in their individual showcases already showed up their individual merch. We'll take a look at it, and now our time, we'll start with Ina!
My merch was... Takodachi ramen stopper!
Basically, I think there's a few people who don't know how to use it. Basically, when you you know cook cup noodles and the lid kind of like always like lifts up, you put that little taco ramen stopper on top of it so that the lift the you know the lid lid doesn't lift
Basically, I think there's a few people who don't know how to use it. When you cook cup noodles and the lid always lifts up, you put that little takodachi ramen stopper on top of it so that the lid doesn't lift...
And then and then you you get like the most perfectly cooked ramen, you know, cup noodles.
And then you get the most perfectly cooked ramen, you know, cup noodles.
Or, you know, you can just keep it as a figure. It was you! Oh, that was me.
Yes, so my merch was...
The Hot Phoenix Thermo Bottle and Bottle Case Set!
I'm so happy for this one, because it's thermos. Everybody can use it. You can keep your hot things hot and your cold things cold. It's perfect. And it even has a little blue bug.
Is it thermal?
Yes, it's thermos!
Inside, yeah. And it has you can basically use the the cap as a cup, too!
Inside, yeah. And you can basically use the cap as a cup, too!
Big brain! I keep forgetting.
Yeah. So after me was... Kanata! Kanata, where should go?
Are you looking for a lovely gift for your significant other? Perhaps you just want to look cool wherever you go. Anyone can wear this cool piece of ice. What is it?
It's the Mori Calliope Pendant.
You can also just display it in your house, because why not? Why not? Why not? I'm genuinely asking you, why not buy it?
Please, please buy one!
Thank you, everyone. Appreciate you. Okay.
Gura! Boobity boobity boob ba! What was your merch?
Bag.
There it is.
Tell us about it.
Bag. Back. Bag.
What kind of bag is it?
What kind of bag?
Blue bag! Blue bag! The shoulder bag!
Bag with strap! Bag with strap! It's so cute!
Oh, so cute! You can fit so much in it. I want one!
And what inspired after? My...
And what inspired it? My...
yam, yam, yam, yam, casual outfit.
That's right!
This is the outfit you're wearing now.
No.
Not this.
Not this, not this. Not your uniform.
It's like someone stole your sweater and made a bag out of it.
Yeah. That's not the worst thing that they made.
Ah, that's a good point.
Okay, and then a tissue.
A tissue.
Who is next?
Last but not least, we had Amelia Watson!
Come on over. Hey.
Ta-da!
Ta-da-da-da! There we go!
Woah! Oh my god!
You can get the hat!
I'm wearing right now!
I'm wearing it right now!
Ah, that's right. On sale today.
Can I take it off and try it on?
No.
Come on.
Why not?
I want to sniff it.
Well, I like hats.
Do you guys going to do weird stuff with it, like smell it?
I want to smell it.
That hat does not smell like Amelia Watson, okay?
That's a lot.
It's not tinted.
Make it smell like you.
They look so good.
Yeah, make it smell like you.
They haven't been on sale yet, but they will go on sale after this stream.
Speaking of which, there's one more thing.
Oh wait, there's more! What do we got?
What do we got? Ta-da!
Ta-da!
Just kidding.
Yours, we have acrylic stands, too.
These will be out on sale March 5th right after this stream.
Please check the shop page for details. Let's take a look at them.
Can we take my sword?
Ta-da!
Insert.
We can all do our poses.
Yeah. Oh, yeah.
I'm holding an invisible book.
Okay, pose, pose. Wait. Pose, baby, pose.
Wait, give your best lady.
You do it?
Nice.
Yay!
So, if you want these at home, you can buy them together or you can buy them separately, however you want.
Wow, they look really cute.
I deal.
Haha.
So, how did you guys, yeah, what did you guys think about these?
I think they're really cute.
Okay, how was it so far, guys?
It was so fun!
It was so fun.
Everybody did have fun.
I'm so happy.
I'm so glad.
I'm so happy you got to call up.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
We're together, we're together, we're together, we're together, we're together, we're together, we're together.
We're together, we're together, we're together, we're together, we're together, we're together, we're together, we're together, we're together.
Can we have a little request?
Nani, nani?
What happens?
Can we hug? A hug?
A hug?
Ah, you smell good.
Ahara.
I love everyone.
Happy.
Happy, everyone.
It's so cute.
Yay!
So we're back, uh, really healthy.
Everything.
We want, we want.
Every talk a little bit about our, uh.
Our our this this collab.
Maybe pick up some comments.
How's it going, guys?
Did you post some screenshots?
#Myth3Dkitaaa!
Hope you did.
Snippity snip.
Group titty.
Yes.
What was your favorite part to hear?
Tenderm.
I'm asking you guys, too.
What was your favorite part?
Finally, game fun. Game fun.
Game fun. That was fun.
I like beating up Amelia.
And I did not like that.
Yeah, you did.
You're lying to us.
She likes it.
She really likes it.
Yeah.
She wanted it.
Her dream came true.
Yeah, fantastic.
Yay, yay.
SS performance.
They're like the song they're talking about the music.
Exercises.
I only wish we had more.
You wish we had more?
I think they want some.
There might be more.
That is very possible.
Of course I promise you, pinky promise.
That there will be more.
That's right.
Now a performance.
One or two, who knows?
It's coming up.
Alright.
But we got to go to the stage for that.
Okay.
We're going right. Which way is it?
I don't know.
Thank you for the ki-set, bye-bye.
We're flying so fast.
We're sticking out.
Yay, yay, yay, yay!
All right, we love you.
Which way should we go?
Which way are we going?
I don't know.
This way? This way?
Ikuzo!
This way, this way.
We're loading screens, too.
We love the loading screens.
Come on, girls. Check like this.
This way.
Some "once upon a time" is not where our myth belongs
Through the faded lines of words and rhyme is a hidden song
Though fractured deeply, worn by sorrows from time and time again
Take my hand and enter our "pretend"
By star-lit skies, endlessly writing
Inviting those along
Lost souls who hear our song when gone astray
Though strife's part of life, stay unafraid, now
When forces say "behave"
We say instead, "be brave"
In a desperate shout, our souls reach out
With pen toward every page
We ignite, come alive like a starry night
With a fire no doubts can take away
Got no fairy tale where "love prevails"
Though painful, now we move endlessly on
By the light, your spark
Head first, into the dark
Some "once upon a time" is not where a voice gets heard
Will the faded lines of speeding time make us flightless birds?
When pen is running dry, a soul on fire is driven to react
And when burning flames attack,
we will never fade to black
Though fake, it seems, not a dream or a trick of light
Always vacancy, take a seat, it’s our story's time
A world is brought to life, through voices five
And as "real" as they say
Pen as sword, we’re choosing fate
We can never lose our way
By star-lit skies, endlessly writing
Inviting those along
Lost souls who hear our song when gone astray
Though strife's part of life, stay unafraid, now
When forces say behave
We say instead, be brave
Defiant 'til the end, I'll stay killing to sing
I'll dance in burning embers unyielding
Your love's given me wings
In a desperate shout, our souls reach out
With pen toward every page
We ignite, come alive like a starry night
With a fire no doubts can take away
Write a fairy tale where "love prevails"
Cliched, maybe, we move joyfully on
take off and fly
the longer we wait, the stronger it makes us as we fight every fate
strength to finally defeat
this journey a thousand years to meet
take off and fly
the longer we wait,
the stronger it makes us as we fight every fate,
strength to finally defeat,
this journey a thousand years to meet.
a song in snow, enchanted by rhyme,
painted in wishes granted by time.
our longest hopes, connecting, yet those,
feel like echoes of ages gone by.
made a splash, but found I'm not free,
a fish out of water, bound to the sea.
yet a reckless high tide brought you right by my side,
I bet this moment's a wave we can ride.
connecting songs across the sky.
take off and fly,
the longer we wait,
the stronger it makes us as we fight every fate,
strength to finally defeat,
this journey a thousand years to meet.
witness the fire in our minds, burning inside,
rising again from the ashes,
every bruise, any scratches make us feel more alive.
we never give up, never give in, no matter what's ahead,
instead, we'll crush our worries aside.
if there's no world for us to touch or to see,
we'll make it ourselves then make memories,
there ain't a mystery our brains cannot solve,
we just shine brighter, grow tighter, evolve.
connecting songs across that wall
take off and fly,
the longer we wait,
the stronger it makes us as we fight every fate,
strength to finally defeat,
this journey a thousand years to meet.
at the end of this world,
where's our fighting chance?
nothing's changing,
it's always the same story staged with a different dance,
seek out a happy end for me, my friends,
and those who've loved us up 'till now,
I wanna see your smile,
find my way to you somehow.
take off and fly,
the longer we wait,
the stronger it makes us as we fight every fate,
strength to finally defeat,
this journey a thousand years to meet.
let's try, it can't be denied,
the wish in my heart is you, right here by my side,
strength is all that we'll need,
I won't wait a thousand years to meet.